[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ a limit on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It would not be ____ to deviate from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is feared that disagreement about what to do in Iraq will ____ the relationship between the USA and the UK.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a hostile or abusive work ____ which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The report shows how the mass media indirectly ____ adolescent smoking rates.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your target heart ____ is a useful way of pacing yourself during exercise.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a stereotype of ____ victims.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please ____ in the cafeteria after lunch.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The university's plan to ____ more students from poor backgrounds is an exercise that is not certain to succeed.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The first ____ of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To justify their high salary, top managers like to ____ to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The internet allows people to ____ whatever they want without needing to go to the shops.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The goal is to ____ world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and service within the broad area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Very few companies can ____ cars of the quality of German makes such as BMW or Mercedes.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people are unwilling to ____ the issue of global warming. They claim it is not happening.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to ____ in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to connect more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "From the outset of the gulf crisis, President George Bush stated that it was not his ____ to harm the Iraqi people.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the ____ to the general public in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to interrupt the ____ of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The minister was unwilling to ____ on the changes in the price of oil in the next few months.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our teachers ____ the school's philosophy that only excellence is good enough.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These instruction and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are ____ (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to ____ the person and the institution of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I gave him clear ____ how to do the experiment, but he obviously wasn't listening.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The xenon atoms need to ____ to a speed of 30 km/s.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The book is an educational and approachable reference in a difficult ____ of medicine where clinicians often feel uncertain.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to exert its ____ to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities ____ so naturally as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is taking advice from experts on how to ____ the increase of illegal immigrants.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ is the most common teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Successful applicants will have to provide evidence of medical insurance for the ____ of their stay in the Ukraine.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Weight loss is a constant ____ for many Americans.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Bible laid down some rules for the humane ____ of slaves but did not condemn the practice.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to the new law, smokers will now have to ____ the pleasure of a cigarette with their drink in a restaurant or bar.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Her problems began to ____ themselves after she was absent for more than a month.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the ____ of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The union leaders promised to ____ for a longer lunch break for the employees.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Gandhi, who brought independence to India, was an ____ man.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is feared that disagreement about what to do in Iraq will damage the ____ between the USA and the UK.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot comply with this law due to ____ of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government failed to understand why the people were so unhappy with its policies, and ____ was voted out at the next election.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to criticize the boss in front of all the workers.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The number of students in the school will continue to ____ in the next few years as Frankfurt increases in popularity.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you make an ____ effort, you still have a chance to pass your exams.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It started to ____ after much questioning that the reasons for his bad behaviour were problems at home.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you ____ the page, you will see the map I would like you to copy.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's a ____ problem, and its solutions will require new technology, policy, awareness and education.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are an individual with a permanent disability, you may be eligible to ____ a discount.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To launch the project, a special ____ will commence at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government failed to suppress street demonstrations ____ its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to ____ the vast mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some, but not many, drivers do not ____ to increases in the price of petrol by using their car less frequently.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Let's make it clear from the beginning that there is no one thing that you can do to ____ everyone, or even to ____ the same person every time.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his career in ____ to assure his political survival.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He alleged that the state had adopted the policy of attacking the ____ independent media rather than targeting individual journalists as in the past.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mild pain and inflammation can often ____ an otherwise rewarding day of skiing.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is a very trivial example for demonstration purposes. However, the effect is ____ for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next stage of the writing process is to ____ it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the manner that best fits local ____ and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They met resistance from Nigerian government officials who did not welcome change and did not want to hear the ____ about the AidS epidemic in Nigeria.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her chances of success in the examinations will continue to ____ unless she starts working harder very soon.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "One of the most common laments we hear from instructor is that they can't get their students to ____ substantial revisions.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was also no apparent record of an attempt to measure the ____ between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The business is hoping to ____ into new markets in Africa.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our chief problem is how to ____ the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had found a large ____ of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are encouraged to commit to the therapy group for a sufficient ____ of time before deciding that it is not the right treatment for you.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are an ____ with a permanent disability, you may be eligible to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He had to ____ the fact that teaching was not the right job for him.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The relationship between Christianity and the Enlightenment remains a ____ issue in the history of Western civilization.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Such web content does not necessarily ____ the opinions of the University administration.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you currently do not possess the ____ to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to set up a new computer lab, but the ____ would have been too high.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We held that the entry was illegal because police failed to ____ their purpose before using the crowbar to pry the door open.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This tells us that there is a very large market for us to expand into, if we take ____ of the opportunities as they arise.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ how much people should or should not drink.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most important ____ to her learning is that she never does her homework.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you ____ your application in person, there will be a delay of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "At this stage of our research we were unable to find a ____ for accessing the actual decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The syllabus must ____ how attendance and participation affect, if at all, the student's course grade.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While a ____ degree of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually underlie exceptional performance ____ out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Despite the fact that this was a simple questionnaire, the researchers did not even ____ to translate it for use with less educated deaf people.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Check the ____ below for specific dates and starting times.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Victims of terrorist attacks are usually given ____ by the government.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although consultation between students in solving problems is encouraged, ____ answers will be considered plagiarized.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Despite the ____ amount of effort invested in her language teaching she was not able to construct grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People who move from the countryside to a large city often take time to adjust to ____ living.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government had to retreat from its starting position in the face of ____ criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At a ____ point in your journey, you might discover that the topic you chose is just too vast.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Food prices are ____ rising again after many months of no change.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He certainly could not ____ the existence of major problems.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is the ____ of every teacher to be prepared for class and to do everything he or she can to help the students learn.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The dentist needed to ____ my back tooth. It had become badly infected.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A student seeking a ____ in this field of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "At weddings the speeches usually ____ the food.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His behaviour has not been very ____ since he returned from vacation.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to ____ as educational institutions and. business corporations seek new ways to expand their services.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since we can't observe it directly, we need to ____ it from the things we can observe.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some institutions did not ____ these issues because they predicted them and dealt with them in advance.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They were small-minded people and could not ____ students who were superior them.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is set to suffer a heavy defeat in the vote to ____ its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his duty to correctly ____ the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teacher made the spontaneous ____ to take her class out to the playground and finish the lesson there.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to intervene in the ____ over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Since it was founded in 1999, the partnership program has been a key ____ in the dramatic increase in applications to the College.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Why do people still ____ in living near volcanoes?", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure ____ the head, damaging the interior of the brain.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the ____ that publishing houses lack sufficient diversity in both high and middle-level staff members.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The essential ____ for successful teaching is the ability to interest the students.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no need to enumerate in ____ the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too ____ a method of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has done a ____ with the nurses union in order to avoid strikes in hospitals.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Msall said that while the ____ has improved, the numbers haven't been changing fast enough.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The German government should have realized that it would ____ matters by allowing the different German states to have their own regulations about smoking in public buildings.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that ____ is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This document explains why it is important to ____ a community assessment during a sustainability project.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This means that you will be able to ____ money from your bank account to your StanfordCardPlan using this new online service.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people use unethical methods to create a ____ that says what they want it to say.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The notion of the student as the school's primary customer provides an important guiding ____ for many of today's school reforms.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Iraqi regime failed to take that final ____ to cooperate with the United Nations investigation.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is having difficulties getting people to change their ____ toward use of public transportation.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He questioned the security coordination that enabled the terrorists to ____ all their preparatory work. The authorities had failed to surround the school for three days.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I suspect that problems at home are the reason for her poor ____ in school.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The topic of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could ____ fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I think her problems in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The hypothesis put forward in this paper depends in no ____ upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed ____ of the student and signed consent of the parent.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is an ____ pattern to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her chances of success in the examinations will continue to ____ unless she starts working harder very soon.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Never has the ____ of a stable, prosperous, and democratic hemisphere seemed so close within reach.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most common ____ of a cold is a runny nose.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the ____ between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Your ____ is to learn the English words that will help you be successful in your school subjects.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Carla Santos, a professor of leisure studies, says our perception of another culture is ____ shaped by accounts of travel writers, who tend to perpetuate cultural stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school does not have ____ money to build a new cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to ____ a trend such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is in a very good ____ to the north of Frankfurt and on the edge of the beautiful Taunus forest.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to ____ the directions of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I'm not sure that his parents realize the ____ of the problems he is having in school.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to ____ the progress of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police did not have the necessary ____ to cut the man free from the crashed car.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "At this ____ of our research we were unable to find a means for accessing the actual decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Successful applicants will have to provide ____ of medical insurance for the duration of their stay in the Ukraine.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Aqaba ____ (see fig. 11.6) would pump sea water during off-peak periods.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your ____ grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will definitely fail this course.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding ____ sentences that contradict common sense.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to represent information about patterns of ties ____ social actors.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police ____ gave a very different version of the incident than the TV reporter the previous day.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "At first there was a little ____ between the Japanese and Korean students, but this soon passed.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to resign over the ____ in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was ____ a huge amount for a programme that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If mobile phones ____ any further, the keys will be too small to use.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the ____ support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this class, we will examine the ____ about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He has only ____ control of basic verb grammar. He quite often chooses the wrong tense or forgets the -s ending.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The imaginary problem results from the authors' ____ misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the classroom doors to make them less easy to break down.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "too"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to impose an artificial ____ upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government will ____ in the coming election how unpopular its politics have been.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to resign over the ____ in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's efforts to increase business over the past year failed to ____ the shareholders.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In order to get people to change unhealthy habits, the government needs to use a ____ of the carrot and the stick.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Al Gore absolutely did not ____ the Nobel peace prize. On a personal level, he has not reduced his own carbon dioxide emissions.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company made a radical reduction in its workforce in order to improve its ____ in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students worked in groups to ____ (or dis____) a series of mathematical statements.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All this progress was a ____ of the advance of technology and also of advances in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "____ments cannot govern without the broad assent of the people.", "Opt_1": "Govern", "Opt_2": "Evolve", "Opt_3": "Manufacture", "Opt_4": "Ignore", "Answer": "Govern", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He was not willing to ____ from previous legal commitments.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Modern computers can store the ____ of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Parental assistance should be just sufficient to get the learner past his ____ difficulties.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Before the accident he did not ____ his guns locked or unloaded; now he does.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To remain ____ for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory progress toward a degree according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Nadeem has worked with FSU London since early 2004 as a permanent ____ of staff managing the Information Technology Systems.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There's no need to give an ____ answer, Two or three short sentences will be enough.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company plans to ____ training videos on its intranet website.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To qualify for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a ____ efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ what people actually do in practice as far more significant and worthy of formalization than what ivory-tower logicians prefer in principle.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Letter from the headmaster to parents: 'We ____ that the school will be closed for the next two days because of problems with the heating system.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The internet has made it possible for a community of people with ____ interests to get together online, even if they don't live close to each other.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A popular type of TV ____ shows people who escape the contemporary world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new teacher looks quite young but his ____ age is 55.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging ____ for the employers to determine the factors that stimulate job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will ____ no credit for work that has simply been copied from the internet.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This has been the ____ of scientists and engineers for many years and has only recently been considered a hot research topic with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There were many sane but ____ reasons why he gave up his well-paid job.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most important ____ of the new design is that it consumes less power.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government intends to found a new organization to help young people find ____ jobs.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "By running these ads, the newspaper is sending the message that it considers this a ____ product to sell.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a ____ final exam.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is overspending and will soon ____ all the money set aside for books and other materials.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to organize his ____ to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is a common ____ that the universe is infinite. But who knows? Maybe one day we will discover it has an edge or end.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Did you ____ the book that was taken from your bag?", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to ____ or postpone the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is a ____ in my family for everyone to get together for Sunday lunch.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to ____ in a way beyond words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to retain their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to ____ the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has done a ____ with the nurses union in order to avoid strikes in hospitals.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you are interested in checking out any of the books in the display case, please ____ at Circulation.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The head teacher could not ____ parents that there would be no increase in school fees.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much credit by conducting a retreat after all the ____ officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "superior", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This project involves students in the process of learning in an attempt to ____ their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an automatic decision to offer or ____ admission.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company had to amend their ____ predictions after the cost of oil doubled within 6 months.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The intelligence service is finding it very difficult to determine which young men are ____ to become terrorists and which are not.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you plan for your child to ____ the school, you must submit an online request.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to multiply as educational institutions and. business corporations seek new ways to ____ their services.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Even the older ____ does have some command of the Indonesian language.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The atmosphere between the workers and the management improved when ____ working time was introduced.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It seems ____ that precise measurements of the ratio of positive to negative responses will help to decide between the several processes.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The manager used the ____ of the opening of the new factory block to make a speech about future developments.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Tourists who visit a foreign city often employ a ____ to show them the most interesting things to see.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teachers do not always immediately ____ bad behaviour in class. Sometimes it is better to have a quiet talk with the student at the end of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Previous studies have shown that children have ____ difficulties with mathematical equivalence problems.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The report shows how the mass media indirectly ____ adolescent smoking rates.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "All political parties have websites these days to ____ people of their policies.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Drivers who do not park in the ____ places on city streets often come back to find their car has been towed away.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During this course you will review your knowledge of German, by focusing on the four language skills, ____ speaking, listening, reading and writing.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has banned smoking in ____ all public places.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The opening of the new sports ____ was the biggest operation in the school's history.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can indirectly ____ the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Weight ____ is a constant struggle for many Americans.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new committee just adds another ____ to an already complex decision -making process.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The drive to excel must be ____ in the culture of a university.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school is working on a ____ to give all students a portable computer for use in lessons.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to ____ food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These ____ and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable expense to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Your ____ was unclear. Could you please repeat it.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Vehicles that do not display a ____ parking permit will be towed immediately.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was an ____ that had such a deep effect on me that it helped me decide to move back to Prague.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The detective was able to ____ from the size of the footprints that the thief was probably a woman or child.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Even though you may know your housemates well, you should always take the ____ to lock the door. Windows should also be secured.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since the U.S. flu vaccine supply was cut in half early this month, shots are scarce, lines long and some people are ____ to miss out.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have not yet mastered ____ grammar. You still make mistakes like \"he go\" or she don't\".", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The volume of business between Europe and Asia has ____ increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I am hoping that the students will ____ a non-native speaker onto the school council.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If he was indeed employed by the Grand Duke, that would ____ for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was a ____ move, but frankly we didn't have a choice.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a ____ domestic situation would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The revolutionary ____ must come from those basic human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The main ____ to such Research & Development programs is the fact that the market size and the prices of the new products are unknown.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I asked for a concise ____ of what happened. So why have you given me a 20-page report?", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Nowadays nobody attempts to ____ that smoking is bad for the health.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Now retired and free to speak out about the scandal, Karpinski is devoting herself to publicizing her ____ of event.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more ____ policy positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The goals are to answer some of the most ____ questions to advance significantly our scientific knowledge about Mars.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It offers an effective solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills ____ as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The goals are to answer some of the most ____ questions to advance significantly our scientific knowledge about Mars.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a tough ____, but ultimately I think it was the student life that had the greatest impact on my ____ to come to Wheaton.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The beauty of the telephone, and something that the telegraph lacked, was that it required no ____ to operate.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the ____ things that they came up with was that the various government agencies did not connect the dots.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "But when planned and deliberate policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war ____ Iraq.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Google uses a unique computer program to ____ its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I have no ____ of being a teacher when I leave school. I want to earn more money!", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "One of the earliest uses of coffee was actually as a medicine, although there was also a ____ as to whether it was helpful or harmful.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite ____ today but was not apparent before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The town council has been criticized for not providing enough ____ for young people in the town.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Customers found no benefit in ____ -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging task for the employers to ____ the factors that stimulate job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Tests are valid when they ____ what they claim to ____, and reliable when they ____ consistently.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Government ministers laid flowers at the ____ of the terrorist explosion.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a ____ analysis, thus it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Three teachers are going to ____ at the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My family can't ____ a new house. They're so expensive in Germany.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Should the government ____ more in solar energy or nuclear energy? It's a difficult choice.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When you employ an electrician to do a job in your house, you hope they will be ____ at their job.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In an article in the March 11, 2004 ____ of Nature, the investigators report that female mice retain the ability to make new egg cells well into adulthood.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The aquarium owner decided sometime in the spring of 1992 to ____ the animal before any further damage or an accident with the other dolphins could occur.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will ____ by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All students whose college/university will be forwarding tuition payments will need to contact the OSA to find out the ____ procedure.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material ____ of Louisiana, it did not diminish the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In about 5 billion years, the sun will ____ its fuel supply, and will puff up into a bloated star called a red giant.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students need to ____ with the department offering the master's degree to ensure the correct credential courses are taken.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new policy means that faculty members can no longer ____ or modify grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company won the ____ to supply the government with 30,000 special computers for primary schools.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Perhaps it is unfortunate that humor, by its nature of being based in ridicule, will always ____ someone.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My family can't ____ a new house. They're so expensive in Germany.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's a bit surprising at first, how easy it is to measure such a huge ____ as the earth.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The practice test materials will become available just ____ to the class.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The American colonists did not establish a real newspaper of their ____ for another century.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can't always ____ what happens to you, but you can always ____ how you react to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He naturally failed to ____ the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students choosing this option must select a faculty adviser from the departmental faculty who will ____ the student's program.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The internet allows people to ____ whatever they want without needing to go to the shops.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Fish farming is an ____ that should go some way to compensating for the reduction of fish in the oceans.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If the applicant waits until the time of decision to complete this form, it can cause a serious ____ in obtaining the visa document.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed assent of the student and signed ____ of the parent.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Three teachers are going to ____ at the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Modern computers can ____ the equivalent of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ will move to a 42-volt electrical system within this decade.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Latin alphabet did not ____ between the vowel and consonant sounds of i and u.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Before doing a longer piece of writing it is usually a good idea to make an outline to organize your ____ ideas.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking point within the sentence, for ____ before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How can the traditional classroom and the technology in it ____ deeper learning?", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The dentist needed to ____ my back tooth. It had become badly infected.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I'm in a ____ with John's parents. They want me to give him more homework, but I know he won't do it.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you ____ your application in person, there will be a delay of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I don't think the government will manage to ____ many people to recycle more of their garbage.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Congress is resolved to ____ online gambling in America.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This survey examines attitudes ____ the campus-area housing market.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not ____ it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to extend a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has only had ____ success in reducing the number of unemployed people.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Individuals should report the incident to a faculty or ____ member at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The contributors ____ that teaching is a gendered occupation with low status and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar symbol of ____ to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is now obvious to almost everyone that the decision to invade Iraq was a very ____ error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government does not plan to ____ any more immigrants unless they can prove that their life is in danger in their own country.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To test for a ____ sentence, see if it can stand alone and still mean something.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs generally will not lead to a poor choice; it will only ____ the analysis.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His research helped establish that ____ DNA sequences may behave differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ what a woman should do with her body.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we want to maintain support for an open and ____ economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Did everyone ____ their report card.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Miller, long a ____ of Switzerland, broke with the school of traditional psychoanalysis over the issue.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Using computer modeling, he was able to ____ the relationship between the strength of a stellar wind and the age of a star.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a ____ speed at all heights.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The instructor is expected to ____ his or her grading policy at the beginning of the course.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We do not yet know the ____ for the government of the rapid rise in house prices.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ between mother and child is said to be the strongest of any personal relationships.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Biological processes interact strongly with ____ and chemical processes to create the planetary environment.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How can I ____ access to my Web pages?", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Digital Libraries constitute a relatively young scientific field, whose life spans ____ the last fifteen years.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Business Index provides a one-stop ____ of information on: small business management, foreign trade opportunities, job hunting strategies.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company was unable to ____ its recent good trade figures.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to ____ that none of them could hope to prevail over all the others.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Due to the recent increase in student numbers, the school can now ____ to build a new science laboratory.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The priests of this institution did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the ____ of dreams", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Follow these recommended times for storage in the freezer to enjoy the best quality in flavor and texture and to ____ good nutritive value.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new economies of Chile and Costa Rica have little ____ for poor, unskilled and uneducated workers.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They failed to publicly reinforce the message that climate change will having a direct negative impact on ____ security.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The manager has decided ____ a committee to investigate the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The proposed system seems an improbable target for the short-term, given that a half century of work with this ____ has met only limited success.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This also helps you ____ which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a result of the massive amount of ____ for evolution accumulated over the last two centuries, we can safely conclude that evolution has occurred.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The headmaster called a meeting to try to ____ the dispute between the two teachers.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Younger students usually have no ____ in what they study.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most countries have a ____ by which parents can decide if a film is suitable for their children.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The need for an ____ route to teacher certification has become evident.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They will have to live without their family member for the rest of their life due to this terrible form of cancer and they will ____ to be compensated.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to ____ a photograph when you apply for a job.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting ____ to raise water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There are very few people living today who were born ____ to the first world war.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Can you please ____ how to make a table in Microsoft Word. I've read the instructions but don't understand them.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will ____ by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should not ____ the costs, minimize the benefits of what we have already achieved, or downplay the risk of failure to persevere.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school cafeteria has made the ____ decision not to offer hamburgers, hot dogs and French fries to the younger students .", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The United States is a nation pulling ____ to a degree unknown in the last 25 years.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She has ____ problems with her spelling, but the content of her writing is actually very good.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not ____ our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is a ____ privilege to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad attitude is put on a ____. If the ____ is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government failed to keep its promises and naturally was voted out of ____ at the next election.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can lessen your risk of getting a cold in the winter if you ____ others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In my opinion the government's ____ for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will ____ a lengthy, very technical email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some teachers believe that it is better to teach language to a class with students of ____ ability.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Director develops and oversees an ____ program of professional development and leadership training for history and social science teachers.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is ____ that any complex society will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to represent information about patterns of ties ____ social actors.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot ____ its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The university should not ____ students who take an extra year to complete their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of the Olympic Games is five overlapping rings.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and ____ problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As maintenance requirements and costs increase, fewer aircraft will be in a satisfactory ____ of readiness or mission-capable.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The priests of this ____ did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the interpretation of dreams", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The world's largest film ____ is in Hollywood, Los Angeles.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new team coach is an ____ of the view: No pain, no gain!", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I am no ____ in animal behavior, but anyone with even a slight knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new factory near the school will ____ parts for mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bradley Hall provides backyard ____ to the lakeshore path, and tennis courts are adjacent to the building for your recreational enjoyment.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their instinct whether it is safe to ____ a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ that we consider our own faults before we are too loud about the faults of others.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is a truism that death - not just our own - affects all of us, even if it is a topic most people do not want to ____ for long.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government needs to provide a better ____ for people to save more of their money.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Because of their behavior in protecting food sources, it is ____ unusual to see two hummingbirds spending time together.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you want to know whether an ____ is common or not, look it up in Google.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She has made ____ good progress this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ to one set of religious beliefs and pioneered a new artistic style known today as symbolism.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school can ____ that parents communicate by email, but they cannot insist on it.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company director decided to ____ his son as the new head of marketing.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government shows little ____ into the reasons why so many young people become addicted to drugs and alcohol.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My biggest ____ about the book is that Gruchy did not insert his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "European countries have decided to ____ in an effect to reduce illegal immigration.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Questioning the values of parents is ____ in being a teenager.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Asian companies are good at building small cars but will never ____ the mainstream US car market.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is going to fail the ____ unless there is a drastic improvement in her efforts.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "No matter how we talk and discuss normally, we now have to ensure that the way we talk must not offend any religious, ethnic, cultural, or ____ group.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You are more ____ to get a better grade if you check your work carefully.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Desdemona is ____ for much of the play and when she dies at the end, she takes the blame for her death.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the ____ with a valid excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to exert its ____ to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This ____ is not rare: 99 percent of patients experience a phantom pain after an amputation.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The significant differences between the traditional and non-traditional student has prompted the question whether institutions need to ____ their teaching methods to fit the needs of the non-traditional student.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If a person tends to be ____ in relationships or at work, it is likely that her investment decisions will also be ____.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some tests may be very ____ but too costly to run, while others are less costly but not as precise.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Carla Santos, a professor of leisure studies, says our perception of another culture is likely shaped by accounts of travel writers, who ____ to perpetuate cultural stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An error will ____ if this software is not installed on the user's machine.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students will undertake comprehensive analysis of ____ works and will compile a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to allocate money ____ to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can ____ the diagnosis of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's ____ and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "His behaviour has not been very ____ since he returned from vacation.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a solution to this problem I ____ that all negotiation parameters be delimited at the end.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You need to be careful not to ____ people that you meet on the internet They may not be who they claim to be..", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many schools in poorer parts of the world do not have ____ books and computers to give their students a good education.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to ____ an offer of the local food.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company has ____ plans to increase its business by 50% in the next two years.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "During various stages of a planning process, review and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not ____ one another.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Advertising agencies are always looking for ____ ways to sell boring product like washing powder or packet soups.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Once a language has less than about a hundred speakers, it is almost impossible to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his ____ to correctly inform the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase ____ of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this next ____ you need to cooperate with the person sitting next to you.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a ____ privilege to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For some older people the ____ to new technologies has not been very smooth.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you work harder, you will ____ a better grade next term.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Scientists ____ that most children born today in First World countries will see their 75th birthday.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Matilda Thurston considered who was the most ____ architect to design a proper campus for 200 students.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was also faced with difficult questions about the university's handling of the emergency and whether it did enough to ____ students.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you ____ your efforts you have a good chance of exiting ESL at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These drug companies were extremely negligent in that they failed to ____ consumers of the potential dangers associated with the use of their products.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Customers found no ____ in comparison -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not exhibit any ____ of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "But when planned and ____ policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To justify their high salary, top managers like to ____ to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The decision on whether to shut down its nuclear power stations is ____ the most serious issues facing the government.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This page includes ____ relating to the continuing controversy over the teaching of evolution and creationism in schools.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The prompt response of the Hu Jintao government has won ____ praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Among the issues that may be examined include whether personal trainers should be held to a higher standard than other ____ professionals.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge related to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more ____ tasks.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There has been a recent ____ in language teaching towards more grammar and vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must struggle with the death ____ regularly.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is an ____ pattern to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States ____ the natural ability to regulate food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Listening to the people is an ____ aspect of good government.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You are being quizzed on how well you understand the information in your required readings, so ____ your answers on what is written in the Hunt textbook.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This certificate program is a series of fully online courses that will show you how to ____ and deliver a quality course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Hopkins argues that the district court committed three ____ errors in determining his sentence.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government claims that it invaded Iraq to bring democracy to that country. Many people, however, claim that this is not a ____ reason to go to war.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This past summer, after a vacation to Japan, I realized that what I had been eating in America was not ____ Japanese food.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There will be an ____ of 20 minutes in the middle of the school play.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a uniform ____ to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is often necessary to associate a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data ____ in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He is ____ considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to assume key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They felt this was an unreliable forecast ____ to poor data and that the harvest could in fact increase.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Iraqi regime failed to take that final ____ to cooperate with the United Nations investigation.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They ____ decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People today have become more conscious of their ____ responsibility to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not ____ the level of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dmitrieva and Kuptsova ____ an identical approach and understand culture as a realm of signs and meanings.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These results suggest that being treated as a sex object can undermine women's ____ in stereotypically masculine domains.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most serious ____ to implementing the Convention in Venezuela was clearly the poverty facing a large proportion of the population.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She is yet to master ____ verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will not get a ____ reply to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You do not need to consider the whole of human psychology, but you should make a ____ between good excuses and bad excuses.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students will need to ____ a spokesperson to speak for their group and come to an agreement about their decision.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a ____ policy that can respond and adapt to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "On the ____ occasion when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than pure hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The many demonstrators on the streets of the capital city were a clear ____ of the government's unpopularity.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government failed to meet its ____ of reducing child poverty by 20%.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We did not base our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or ____ of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to ____ its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The document was intended to ____ everything from minerals, through the kingdom of plants, to the highest animals.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing rigid laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not ____ with one another.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government reports a slight ____ in unemployment in the last month.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief ____ for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If breastfeeding is not possible, ____ infant milk formulas are a good alternative.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The rules of the school stipulate that you must leave your ____ phone in your locker and not bring it to class.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This ____ text contains the typical method of trisecting a segment.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The business manager could not ____ the anomaly in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government neither intends to ____ on the event nor even to admit that it actually happened.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teachers are not universally in favour of the school's plan to ____ flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He certainly could not ____ the existence of major problems.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not ____ to 100% because many students were neutral on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In closing, I want to ____ that I know that our community is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a ____ decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and ____ related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Patients are ____ to forget information that is not written down.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In many cases print journals are disappearing as librarians strive to ____ money and shelf space.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Could you use informal writing tasks to ____ thinking and learning?", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Almost all of the world's countries ____ to the United Nations organization.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same strategy could be a road to ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The information that you receive in today's lesson will ____ you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are definitely going to ____ the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your ____ writing must correlate to your research notes, otherwise you risk being accused of plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Banks that adopt the Equator Principles apply them globally to project financing in all ____ sectors including mining, oil and gas, and forestry.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "European democratic nation states have increasingly lost ____ over the conduct of their own economies.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The media and the public should not blame the music ____ for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Infinite ____ is so vast and incomprehensible an idea that the mind of man must necessarily be bewildered in the contemplation of it.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most governments refuse to ____ with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do I have to be a ____ of the Society to submit a paper?", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a ____ final exam.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to allocate money ____ to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Poor diet itself is not a cause of scoliosis, but maintaining a healthy diet can ____ the symptoms of scoliosis.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The German government should have realized that it would complicate matters by allowing the different German states to have their ____ regulations about smoking in public buildings.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school needs to address the serious problem of bullying ____ grade 7 students.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The UK Highway ____ is the book of road rules that must be learned by new drivers.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In fact, the price of ____ is \ufffd\ufffd5000 higher if it lies in a section with the Mississippi river passing.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Recent research shows bias ____ African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Illegal immigration is not the ____ reason so many poor young blacks are on the streets and why some turn to gangs, guns and drug dealing.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The essay asks students to complete several tasks, giving the students ____ examples of human rights cases.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should seriously ____ the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally feasible option.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ we are going to have a test on this. - You are right!", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This international degree course has been especially created for international students in their final ____ of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As long as the person did not consume large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the ____ on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Class data will be collected to compare perceived overweight and attempt at dieting with ____ weight risk classification.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Program is designed to ____ researchers whose ISBM-supported work appears in the academic literature.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The first effort to produce a revised policy started during the mid-1980s and failed to ____ in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Can you ____ these dollars to Yen for me?", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She did not follow the ____ on the label, despite carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to retain their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to ____ the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Furthermore, as an educational institution, the College cannot ____ the background and perspectives of its students and must attempt to promote teaching practices and a campus atmosphere that benefits and ensures the success of all of its learners.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The reduced rainfall of recent years will ____ large parts of the country into desert.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "People who ____ from hay fever cannot have real flowers in their house. They have artificial ones instead.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's hard to ____ the temptation to buy from an unknown company when they're advertising low prices for name brand products.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to ____ problem-solving strategies that offer clear practical solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An employee or University student who wishes the matter to receive a ____ investigation and review should contact the EEO Officer.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is now ____ to almost everyone that the decision to invade Iraq was a very serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this field of study will have abundant opportunities to ____ personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school is will continue to undergo problems in its ____ to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein ____ the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not occupy much space.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The study did not discover any significant ____ between the type of music and the amount of stress.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial choice process, it is important to ____ how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages ____ from a moderate amount of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When used correctly and consistently, condoms are an effective ____ of preventing pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "People who move from the countryside to a large city often take time to adjust to ____ living.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The main ____ of teaching should be to teach the students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The organization has published a ____ of its history since it was founded in 1965.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He ____ failed to mention the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has announced its ____ for the introduction of the new tax system over the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The last ____ of the twentieth century started in 1990 and ended on 31 December 1999.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results suggest that the best models will almost always ____ both vertical and horizontal processes.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Stated simply, this principle ____ that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The study also found that both genders get a similar ____ from the therapy, which reduced mortality risk in women by an estimated 43%.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The proposed system seems an improbable ____ for the short-term, given that a half century of work with this goal has met only limited success.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Media center users must ____ to the same standards of behavior expected of other library visitors.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her sadness when she only came third in the music competition.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must comprise achievement that is over and above ____ course activities.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ much time and effort into marketing its new product.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more moderate ____ positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater magnitude that occurs in a ____ area.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was little ____ to the government's proposals to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is somewhat unusual considering the 1997 survey's ____ of 41%.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will find reference books on this shelf and the ____ ones.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to require food manufacturers to label their products as high-, low- or ____ fat.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors should give ____ advice and treatment to all patients, whether rich or poor.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "No individual can have much ____ on the environment, but people working together can make a big difference.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Chromatography is a separation ____ that is used in virtually all branches of science and technology.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Court did not find it ____ to hear the testimony of the two forensic experts and did not consider the possibility of ordering a further investigation.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The workers did not ____ to lose their jobs. It was the managers who made the mistakes, not them.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is not a defect in the ____ of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government promised to review its ____ on drug criminality.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is a very trivial example for demonstration purposes. However, the effect is ____ for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, owe a huge ____ to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They further alleged that the removal of the soil would ____ the quality of the district's drinking water.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Board of Trustees met in April 2006 to discuss this report, and decided to ____ the construction of a 500 kW turbine.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There are very few people living today who were born ____ to the first world war.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Bone marrow may ____ cells lost in vision diseases.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Since the early 1990s, the number of smokers has continued to decrease but at the more gradual ____ of 5.2% annually.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people have to ____ their houses when war breaks out in their country.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We could not detect any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and ____ of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Oil is becoming more and more scarce. It is ____ that we find new ways of powering cars and industry.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The requirements ____ to decrease family and individual student control over the transition process.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The main ____ of the committee is to recommend a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more secure ____ unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The court decided to ____ the opinion of the mental health specialist.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Odland demonstrated the ability to run a significant ____ with a wide geographical spread.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The drugs are used to ____ performance artificially to the degree that they give athletes a competitive edge.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great distance from her primary ____ as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We have found that students are more likely to ____ a community health project if they join a team.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I usually keep a supply of ____ pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Recent research shows bias ____ African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to ____ an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and ____ factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse ____ of education and research institutions vested in the common goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most western countries want to ____ with China. It's the largest market in the world and its developing fast.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to fail to prepare properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are ____ 350 students in high school. I'm not sure of the exact number.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Through appointments and legislation the President was able to ____ the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds ____ to help students and their families finance the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In most countries the ____ for the place where you can get information is the letter 'i'.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must ____ the following requirements each semester in order to continue receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You should not ____ that the test questions this semester will be on the same topics.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some, but not many, drivers do not ____ to increases in the price of petrol by using their car less frequently.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This famous ____ will assure her place in the history of sport.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ advantages of these close personal relationships far exceed the disadvantages of remaining small.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done ____ the comparison of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding ____ sentences that contradict common sense.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is the room where we ____ the science equipment ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Example: She doesn't have a very good ____ with her parents.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge ____ regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Describe the study in ____ sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is worth investigation.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The monthly mortgage payment is just one of the costs to consider when deciding if you can ____ a home.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government can suggest that people eat more healthily but it cannot ____ them to do so.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some subjects in our school have a higher ____ than others. Everyone wants to take science, but few want to study a second language.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Different ideas about what is fashionable - in clothes, music, etc. - ____ at different times and in different countries.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A major defect in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Major Smith occupied the city as ordered but was unable to ____ the bridge, lacking both a drill and powder.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many language teachers believe that their learners should use only authentic materials, not ones ____ made for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The administration's proposal to ____ the school day came under attack from the teachers.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She has made fairly good ____ this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "John continue to maintain that he gave me his homework, but I'm ____ he didn't.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The study of Growth and Development can help us to know a person more thoroughly and ____ be better doctors.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Where did you ____ your knowledge of ocean ecology?.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The document was intended to ____ everything from minerals, through the kingdom of plants, to the highest animals.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is easy to ____ the government for its failures, but no-one has come up with any better ideas.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Austen does not ____ us that a woman with Jane's mind, integrity, emotional intensity could fall and remain in love with such a dubious character.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most people have a vague ____ of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we want to maintain ____ for an open and dynamic economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The director planned to ____ the information to the workforce at the next general assembly.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The workers were not ____ of the management's plans to relocate the factory.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its constant updating, people will be able to ____ new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Omitting the transportation costs would ____ the company's financial position.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Research shows that earnings ____ strongly with IQ levels.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Each College or School should ____ the teaching of basic technology skills at the earliest level possible.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student who is in ____ to the University at the end of any academic term shall not be permitted to register in the University again.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Another common meaning of ____ is the date on something has to be done, as in Don't forget. Your project is ____ tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Roman Jewish population did not ____ during Sixtus' reign; indeed, there was always movement of Jews in and out of the region.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you talk through a cloth it will distort the ____ of your voice.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school has decided from now on to ____ its Teacher-Parent newsletter on the website, and not on paper.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Rules do not usually stimulate creativity or passion; ____ they demand conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We will not ____ the personal property of co-workers and customers, and will respect their right to privacy.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He came up with a ____ excuse for not doing his homework, but his teacher did not believe him.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I don't understand it. His test scores do not ____ to what I know he knows.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Wildcats, however, were unable to ____ the scoring opportunities into points.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Use this ____ when you need to restore accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There are one or two ____ spelling problems but in general this is an excellent piece of writing.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If he was ____ employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Is this a ____ picture by Picasso or is it a fake?", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Carrying a large ____ of money is not a crime.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "From the airplane it was possible to see the ____ of the destruction caused in the earthquake.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding certain sentences that ____ common sense.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The University may ____ the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written notice to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is a ____ chance to visit South Africa, and at the same time help build a school in the desert.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Thus, the results obtained are ____ with the popular belief that alcohol intoxication causes males to view women as more attractive.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Costrell also ____ it disturbing that the administration failed to exert its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results ____ that the best models will almost always incorporate both vertical and horizontal processes.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Loo (= toilet) is not a word that you should use in ____ situations.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They simply decided for ____ reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Government agencies and aid organizations often failed to ____ people in affected communities about aid distribution and reconstruction.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers need to regularly ____ the quality of their student's work.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Developments in computer technology may eventually make ____ weather forecasting possible.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police need to ____ more evidence before they can make any arrests.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The results indicated that there was a ____ improvement in fluency, a slight improvement in accuracy, but no improvement in complexity.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Distance learning is the most significant ____ occurring in higher education today.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He said the ____ now should exclude events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to achieve the results.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We used this information to ____ a continuous measure of the ratio of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must ____ achievement that is over and above regular course activities.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The two procedures consistently showed that garlic did not ____ the growth of oral bacteria.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is especially true in the environmental sciences where many of the systems are dynamic and ____ complex.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to ____ Nigeria's ever-growing economic problems.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The strategy used for the actual campaign was ____ different.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Significant progress has been toward reaching this goal through the ____ workforce planning effort as well as specific unit managerial decisions.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates ____ to some extent on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is ____ to consider her difficulties at school in the context of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Poor diet itself is not a ____ of scoliosis, but maintaining a healthy diet can diminish the symptoms of scoliosis.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to deprive people of the ____ to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The test will be a ____ of reading comprehension passages and short writing texts.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The media and the public should not ____ the music industry for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new manager needs time to ____ her own style of leadership.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was an ____ in how new communication technologies could serve a community's educational goals.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most important feature of the new ____ is that it consumes less power.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government hopes that its proposals will ____ a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His ____ is that if we don't cut taxes, then unemployment will rise.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Solving a problem of this ____ will require the collective will and shared sacrifice of all members of the university.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The terrorist plane crashing into the New York tower is an ____ that most people will never forget.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the political support needed to ____ funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The recent switch from Webmail to the ____ mail interface was a poor decision.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and ____ decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more secure ____ unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He flew in with 500 rolls of film and 1400 pounds of provisions but forgot to ____ for the pilot to pick him up again.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The department must ensure that all students and faculty members have access to a broad ____ of learning resources.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To remain eligible for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory progress toward a ____ according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The university must not neglect issues which ____ staff and students, in particular graduate students.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He is ____ considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to assume key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Giuliani's leadership during New York City's darkest hours of the September 11th terrorist attacks earned him global ____ and admiration.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Because of the increase in the price of oil the company was unable to adhere to its plans to ____ new workers.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If the student refuses to leave after being requested to do so, the instructor may summon University Police to ____ the student.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many arguments would not ____ if people would define the words they use.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The trial court noted that the newspaper articles ____ reported events and provided no editorial comment.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "sometimes"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This page contains a sample ____ to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong ____.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He said that he did not want to ____ the issue until the committee meeting.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was little ____ to the government's proposals to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Vehicles that do not display a ____ parking permit will be towed immediately.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The website shows how schools ____ and use their resources.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This project will ____ in a major research essay of 2000 words.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so hostile to allowing ____ parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government minister expressed regret at her thoughtless ____ about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the ____ eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will descend by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a ____ of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next stage of the writing process is to ____ it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The workers were not ____ of the management's plans to relocate the factory.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Force is not always the best tool to get people to change their behaviour, and ____ not their way of thinking.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's no use trying to ____ me that your father speaks 10 languages. I just don't believe you.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A series of accidents and a mounting public ____ resulted in the government licensing of pilots and aircraft.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Scientists are working on a robot that can ____ to the deepest parts of the Pacific Ocean.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "John has many strong opinions. You have to be sure not to let him ____ groupwork in class.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to ____ global problems, since they have also failed to ____ their own domestic problems.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and suggest ____ resolutions.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I ____ myself in a different manner to different people.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "From the outset of the gulf crisis, President George Bush stated that it was not his ____ to harm the Iraqi people.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People are more ____ to migrate in times of war or economic poverty.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company directors are ____ that business will improve in the new year.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He is the inevitable ____ for the leading role in the play. He's by far the best actor in the school.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "At first there was a little ____ between the Japanese and Korean students, but this soon passed.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we assume that the ____ of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Not everyone knows that Texas was once a ____ of Mexico.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Student surveys find teaching to be too uniformly didactic, and their learning too passive. Students report spending ____ class time just taking notes.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Rules do not usually ____ creativity or passion; rather they demand conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A major defect in the proposal is that there is not ____ money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They are quoted at length in Kornbluh's book, The Pinochet File, and ____ cited in the New York Times.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Blair will need to persuade the Americans that Europeans will no longer ____ Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Professor Cowen has a ____ interest in professional service firms and has conducted much of her research in the investment banking industry.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I don't believe that the government's plan to imprison more criminals is the best ____ for the problem of rising crime.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is extremely important that you establish a strong ____ to return to your country after you complete your studies.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I have no ____ to students wearing hats in the classroom, but many teachers do.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government decided to alter its economic ____ after three years of very slow growth.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Because of computer problems there will be a ____ in the announcement of the winner.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After listening to the students' assurance, the ____ decided not to block their plan for a sleepover in the school gym.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is will continue to undergo problems in its attempt to ____ new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not the government's role to ____ what people are doing when they are online.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The boss decided not to ____ her employee's request to leave work early.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to deprive people of the ____ to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Until ____ there have been few sources of information about the morphological and syntactic structure of the Kam language.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government needs to decide on a ____ response to the continuing violent demonstrations.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Through the ____ and its constant updating, people will be able to discover new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I did not ____ my ESL teacher. He was wearing a costume for Renaissance Day.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On the whole the great ____ of Canadian immigration of the past generation has been drawn from the English-speaking countries.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government failed to suppress street demonstrations ____ its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The student could not identify the ____ factors in a solution to the problem.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to ____ any of these abstract terms, and yet I recognize some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is fair to praise the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment ____ older people.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is one of several errors that indicate that your ____ is not set up properly; this can be corrected only by University personnel.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government ____ wrote to confirm that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They simply decided for ____ reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A common science ____ for young people is to investigate the growth of plants under different soil, light and water conditions.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Education has reduced the rate at which the disease has ____ throughout the population.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to impose a ____ on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A significant ____ to setting up a new business is the enormous amount of documentation that has to be completed.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the affair to the general ____ in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is a ____ example of the government passing a law that everyone was happy with.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A student seeking a ____ in this field of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If your reply is not ____ at all to the subject line, start a new thread with a fresh subject line.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We must be ____ in how we interpret the data. It would be easy to draw false conclusions.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The study finds they are more likely than their non-Latino white neighbors to ____ another stroke in the first two years after living through one.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students should discuss ____ options with their academic advisor.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Strict laws in Germany ____ the opening of shops on a Sunday.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Fire Chief Anthony Yenzer said the ____ cause of the fire was determined shortly afterwards through interviews with the two male students.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The evidence is overwhelming that prediction markets provide a more ____ prediction than polls.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If faculty ____ that a mental health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government is going to introduce a law that will ____ smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We will continue to see new immigrants coming to our city, and we will need to ____ their access into the medical care system.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a ____ attempt to conceal the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In issues of accuracy or speed, the ____ must always have priority over the latter.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Leadership is not a ____ that many people have.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He has a ____ knowledge of computer technology.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people claim that the growth of the internet has been to the ____ of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If he doesn't start to ____ his behaviour, he is in danger of being asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The committee will ____ the process by which the decision was made.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I really need one hundred percent concentration while performing my duties; I cannot be ____ messaging.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teachers ____ to improve student scores in standardized tests by doing 5 minutes practice at the start of every lesson.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The assignments and quizzes form an integral part of the course grade and you may not obtain a good grade if you ____ them.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government claims that it invaded Iraq to bring democracy to that country. Many people, however, claim that this is not a ____ reason to go to war.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is ____ knowledge that credit cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is inevitable that any complex ____ will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Very often, in the early summer, the hills are covered during the night by clouds, which do not always ____ until the sun has risen.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The purpose of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the ____ of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This looks like a copy. Can you please give me the ____ sheet.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you work hard all lesson, I will ____ you by letting you go to lunch five minutes early.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to deprive people of the ____ to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "China also experienced social upheaval, and was unable to ____ foreign domination of its trade.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We ____ all our efforts and resources to the education and preparation of all students.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore ____ a nation and created many social problems that did not exist before its invention.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The role of doctors as a conscience of the community deserves more consideration in times of stress and under difficult ____ such as war.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration refuse to modify its goals in order to ____ a consensus?", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Twins born from the same egg are called ____ twins. They look exactly the same. Fraternal twins look a little different from each other.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a strong ____ between what the government promised to do and what it has actually achieved.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to ____ any of these abstract terms, and yet I recognize some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Due to the ____ shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to assemble a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university has no obligation to refund the ____ after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "At the same time, we believe that the victory over ____ and hatred is achieved one person at a time.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "How the ____ changed when he entered a room: it was warm, electric, somehow bigger.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting threaten to raise water levels and ____ flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was not the ____ noise of the battle-front that night; every soldier knew that a something different was going to happen.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of pressure to ____ implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We ____ outside counsel to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}]]